mypurplemartini.com 2017-11-26

# My purple martini

MyPurpleMartini.com ("MyPurpleMartini.com ", "us”,” we" or “website”) respects the privacy of the visitors to its Sites. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms in the MyPurpleMartini.com Terms of Service that you can find at www.mypurplemartini.com and which incorporate this Privacy Policy by reference.

"Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

"Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**User Consent**

By submitting Personal Information through our Sites, You agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Information may be processed by MyPurpleMartini.com.

**General**

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Site.

  * We may collect your name, email address, your gender, date of birth and postal code.
  * We may collect your telephone number from a mobile device and send you messages if you decide that you want to receive SMS, MMS, or other text messages from the Website.
  * When you save other Personal Information in your profile we will collect any such information you enter.
  * When you enter Personal Information throughout the MyPurpleMartini.com network using one of the features of the MyPurpleMartini.com network, for example my page, testimonials, blogs etc. we will collect any such information you enter ("Publicly Posted Information").
  * When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email addresses and any information contained in the email you send us.

Once you register with MyPurpleMartini.com and sign in to our Services or you are responding to an invitation to join MyPurpleMartini.com, you are not anonymous to us. If you are browsing the Sites without being invited or registering with MyPurpleMartini.com, you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information listed below under Personal Information Collected Via Technology. If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the site. MyPurpleMartini.com stores this information to send these invitations, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Use of information**

Any visitor of the Sites can view your profile information and photos that you have uploaded to the MyPurpleMartini.com community. You can control what part of your profile information and photos is visible to visitors of the Sites and which categories of MyPurpleMartini.com users can see what information.

To provide you with some of the features that the MyPurpleMartini.com community offers to its members, we may use your Personal Information, for example to send invitation emails to people that you specified as being interested in joining the MyPurpleMartini.com community, becoming your friend or playing a game on the Sites. We may use your Personal Information to provide useful information about social networks to people who might be interested in joining the MyPurpleMartini.com community, becoming your friend or playing a game on the Sites, for example when we send birthday reminders to MyPurpleMartini.com members or when we send general newsletters to members of the MyPurpleMartini.com community. When you decide to view a Member's profile, we may show that MyPurpleMartini.com Member that you chose to view their profile. When you provide us with your telephone number, we may use the telephone number to send you the communications that you have requested to receive. If you decide to use certain features of the MyPurpleMartini.com network (like my page, testimonials, blogs and the like), some of the Personal Information you entered into your MyPurpleMartini.com profile and any information, including Personal Information, that you enter using one of these features, might be used and displayed.

You can use the search feature to search for other members by different criteria, like name, location, gender or relationship status etc. The Personal Information that MyPurpleMartini.com members enter into the MyPurpleMartini.com profile will be used for these searches.

Please be aware that any information that is publicly posted throughout the MyPurpleMartini.com network can be accessed by every visitor of the Site subject to the privacy options opted by you.

MyPurpleMartini.com may analyze any collected information for its own internal purposes. In addition, MyPurpleMartini.com may remove personally identifying information from collected information to render it anonymous. MyPurpleMartini.com may use Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information in its discretion.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

MyPurpleMartini.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with MyPurpleMartini.com to provide some of the services and features of the MyPurpleMartini.com community and to help us communicate with you. These service providers may use your personal information to communicate with you about offers and services from MyPurpleMartini.com and our marketing partners. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information.

If you decide to use one of the additional services that are offered by our partners, we may forward Personal Information to these partners to enable them to provide the services that you requested.

We also provide information to third-party advertising companies, as described in the next section.

Please be aware that the handling of your Personal Information by our partners or the third-party advertising companies is governed by their privacy policy, not ours.

We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of MyPurpleMartini.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Reporting a privacy violation**

To file a privacy complaint, start the Privacy Complaint Process by contacting the Grievance Officer. At no point will your identity or contact information be released to the uploader without your consent. Our communications to you about this process will be sent to your registered email address.

**First-party claims required**

We do not accept claims on behalf of third parties except in the following situations:

  * the individual whose privacy is being violated does not have access to a computer
  * the individual whose privacy is being violated is a vulnerable individual
  * you are the parent or legal guardian of the individual whose privacy is being violated
  * you act as a legal representative for the individual whose privacy is being violated

We will not accept privacy complaints filed on behalf of:

  * other family members (e.g. husband, wife, cousin, brother, sister)
  * work colleagues or employees (individuals must report themselves)
  * a company

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Sites. These companies may use Personal Information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Sites and other websites, such as time of day of the login, IP address or information about the internet service provider (ISP) or mobile device Carrier, in order to provide advertisements on the Sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Personal Information Collected Via Technology**

As you navigate the Sites, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. If you send SMS, MMS, or text messages to the Services, we will collect the telephone number (if any) from which such communication was sent. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Sites you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our Services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the MyPurpleMartini.com community experience to meet your special interests and needs. If you search the MyPurpleMartini.com community by using a toolbar that MyPurpleMartini.com, or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Sites.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site.

MyPurpleMartini.com may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Sites. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Sites may not work properly.

Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the MyPurpleMartini.com network. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your MyPurpleMartini.com account information is protected by a password that you select..

**Other Sites**

Our provision of a link to any other Sites or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other Sites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside Sites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside Sites.

**Payment Gateway**

If you are making Payment for products of services using Payment method on our website, we shall log the activity about such transactions. However we do not collect or retain any information. We use the third party payment gateways that collect all the financial information about you and you are responsible to read and authorize those third party Payment gateways to process the Payment.

You are further responsible to understand the Privacy Statement of the Payment gateway providing the service and to study the security procedures followed by them.

As on date, we use the services of CC Avenue but may change the Provider in future and you are solely responsible to check the Provider before processing the Payment.

**Regarding Children**

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.

**Report Abuse:**

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

Mr. Saarthak Gupta  
Purple Martini Entertainment Pvt. Ltd.  
9-D, Rajpur Road,  
Delhi – 110054 (India)  
F: +91-11-2396 8674  
E: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

MyPurpleMartini.com may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MyPurpleMartini.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our Sites. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Sites. Continued use of our Sites following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
